ANS Record Group 2: Curatorial, 1858-ongoing
ANS Archives
- Series 15: Alan M. Stahl curator correspondence and other material, 1914-2000, bulk 1982-2000; 13 cubic feet (13 boxes)
  Alan M. Stahl (b. 1947) of Ossining, N.Y., was curator of medieval coins and of medals at the American Numismatic Society from 1980 to 2000. Born in Providence, Rhode Island, Stahl graduated from the University of California at Berkeley (B.A., 1968) and the University of Pennsylvania (M.A., 1973; Ph.D., 1977). His dissertation became the basis of the book The Merovingian Coinage of the Region of Metz (1982), research on which began as a student in the ANS Summer Graduate Seminar (1975). Much of his scholarly work during his time at ANS was concerned with coinage of the mint of medieval Venice, which resulted in the monographs The Venetian Tornesello: A Medieval Colonial Coinage (1985) and Zecca: The Mint of Venice in the Middle Ages (2000), along with numerous articles. Stahl also took in active role in matters pertaining to medals, serving as editor for two volumes of The Medal in America (1988, 1999), as a U.S.A delegate (1987-2000) and executive committee member (1989-2000) of the Fédération Internationale de la Médaille (FIDEM), and as president (1984-1988) and board member (since 1995) of the American Medallic Sculpture Association (AMSA). In addition to his curatorial duties at ANS, Stahl also was responsible for coordinating the selection of recipients for the Society’s J. Sanford Saltus Medal Award and helped to relaunch the Society’s moribund medallic program in the mid-1980s. After leaving ANS, he has served as a visiting professor at the University of Michigan (2000-2001), Rice University (2001-2002), and the University of Notre Dame (2002), and since 2004 he has been curator of numismatics at Princeton University.
  Contains correspondence, conference materials, professional organization mailings, texts of articles and scholarly papers under review, research notes, and records relating to ANS collections, loans, and exhibits. Correspondence includes scholarly discussions among colleagues and the coordination and review of articles for publication, sometimes with the inclusion of photographs of materials under discussion. There are also replies to inquiries from the general public, the importance of which Stahl stressed in a memorandum (May 18, 1993) to staff. This and additional staff memorandums regarding curatorial policies and procedures can be found in the files “Curatorial Memos” and “General Memos.” Also included are correspondence, notes, and other materials relating to his research on Venetian torneselli (1982-1991); letters to students and former students of the ANS Graduate Summer Seminar, including review notes on their papers; submissions, including artwork and photographs, for several medal design competitions, such as the Statue of Liberty (1985-1987), the quincentenary of Columbus’s voyage (1988-1992), the ANS Endowment (1988-1989), and the ANS 125th anniversary (1982-1983), the last of which includes the original artwork submitted by the winning sculptor, Marcel Jovine. In addition there are materials concerning the Saltus Medal Award Committee (1983-2000); exhibits and other special projects relating to ANS collections, including photographs and other items in files on Indian Peace Medals and the J.P. Morgan collection (both of which contain some of the earliest dated items in the records, ca. 1917-1940s), and materials relating to Victor David Brenner, including biographical items, a deed of gift for a Lincoln plaster by him, and material for an article (1986-1988) and an exhibit (1995). Other topics covered include ANS thefts; materials held on temporary loan at ANS as well as the Society’s loans to other organization; the use of computers for collection control; and newsletters and conference materials of various professional organizations, such as the Fédération Internationale de la Médaille (FIDEM) and the American Medallic Sculpture Association (AMSA). The earliest item in the records is a postcard from a "J.S.S." to Bauman Belden (1914) filed with FIDEM materials (1996-2000).
  - Box 1 of 13
    - Cercle de Bourgoigne
    - Dominick Bimann Society
    - Kathleen Deagan – Coin chapter, 1997
    - G. Roberto Foundation, 1997-1998
    - Medieval Latin studies, 1991-1997
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) and AMSA, 1996-1997
    - Arezzo, 1982-1988
    - Frick – Dutch medal loan, 1996
    - Kazov, 1997
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1992 (1 of 2)
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1992 (2 of 2)
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1993
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1994
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1994
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1993
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1994
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1996
    - FIDEM registration, 1996
    - Klosterneuburg, 1992
    - Computer, 1981-1993
    - Saltus, 1996
    - Day Without Art, 1995
    - Southern Coins in Northern European Contexts (talk), 1986
    - John Dotson, Medieval & Renaissance Texts and Studies, 1990
    - Dictionary of the Middle Ages, 1985
    - ANS and Beaux Arts
    - CUNY talk, 1989
    - Renaissance Conference, 1994-1995
    - FIDEM – Cast or Struck – A Medallic Option, 1994
    - Maccabee Mint
    - Lauffer’s Medal Cabinet, 1985
    - Medieval Archaeology, 1988
    - Berkshire Conference of Women Historians, 1986-1990
    - U.S. Industrial Medal – FIDEM, 1983
    - Medal inquiries, 1995
    - Katonah loan, 1994
    - Loans out – Pending, 1985-1994
    - John Dresser collection, 1986-1989
    - Copper plugs in medals, 1987
    - George Washington exhibit
    - Gaettens Columbus medal
  - Box 2 of 13
    - Bourgey book, 1994
    - Dorothy Budd Bartle – Newark Museum, 1990
    - Maya Bismanisj, 1984
    - Edward Grove, 1985
    - Cliff Levy, 1984
    - Elaine J. Leotti – The Medallist, 1985-1991
    - Greg Lyon, 1988
    - John Jermain Slocum, 1986
    - Smedley, Glenn B., 1985
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1992
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1993
    - FIDEM – Newark, 1990 (1 of 2)
    - FIDEM – Newark, 1990 (2 of 2)
    - FIDEM – Medals to Finland – Shipping documents, 1990-1991
    - FIDEM 50 – Traveling exhibits, 1985-1989
    - FIDEM – Contacts, 1987
    - FIDEM – Correspondence, 1989
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1988
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1985
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1983
    - FIDEM – Canada, 1990
    - FIDEM – Registration, 1990 (1 of 2)
    - FIDEM – Registration, 1990 (2 of 2)
    - Summer Seminar, 1981
    - Summer Seminar, 1980
    - MacArthur Foundation fellows program, 1991-1992
    - Coin inquiries, 1993
    - Decoration inquiries, 1993
    - Medals inquiries, 1993
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association) – Correspondence as president, 1985
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association) – Correspondence as president, 1984
    - AMSA publications, 1983-1984
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association) – Correspondence as president, 1983
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1991
    - Bedoukian Festchrift, 1980-1988
    - Summer Seminar, 1992
    - Summer Seminar, 1991
    - Summer Seminar – Hoards
    - Summer Seminar, 1990
    - Summer Seminar, 1989
    - Summer Seminar, 1988
    - Summer Seminar, 1987 (1 of 2)
    - Summer Seminar, 1987 (2 of 2)
    - Summer Seminar, 1986
    - Summer Seminar, 1985
    - Summer Seminar, 1984
    - Summer Seminar, 1983
    - Summer Seminar, 1982
  - Box 3 of 13
    - Newark Museum, 1997-1998
    - International Congress on Medieval Studies – Kalamazoo, 1995
    - Medieval Institute Congress – Kalamazoo, 1999
    - Medieval Institute, 1981-1995
    - Medieval Academy, 1993
    - Medieval Academy – Council, 1998
    - Medieval Academy – 1998
    - Medal Collectors of America, 1998
    - Medal Collectors of America, 1999
    - Marciana Library, 1998
    - Quincentenary medal competition, 1988-1992
    - Endowment medal production, 1989
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association) – Correspondence as president, 1986
    - FIDEM – Entries accepted, 1988-1990
    - Saltus Medal Award Committee, 1983-2000
    - Stephen K. Sher, 1986-1997
    - Mark M. Salton, 1978-2000
    - Guido Veroi – Saltus award recipient, 1983
    - Marcel Jovine – Saltus award recipient, 1984
    - John Cook – Saltus award recipient, 1987
    - Eugene Daub – Saltus award recipient, 1991
    - Mico Kaufman – Saltus award recipient, 1992
    - Ewa Olszewska-Borys, 1993
    - J. Sanford Saltus Award, 1995
    - Nicola Moss – Saltus award recipient, 1996
    - J. Leonda Finke- Saltus award recipient, 1997
    - Helder Batista – Saltus award recipient, 1998
    - Jeanne Stevens-Sollman – Saltus award recipient, 1999
    - J. Sanford Saltus Award, 1999
    - Giovanni Gorini, 1982-1991
    - Ildar Garipzanov, 1998
    - M. Michel Dhenin – coins of Vron and Hordain, 1980
    - A.S. DeShazo, 1982
    - Georges Depeyrot, 1995
    - Farrell – Archaeological Institute of America, 1990
    - Geoff Egan, 1994
    - Mme. Francoise Dumas, 1978-1983
    - John H. Dryfhout – Inventory of Saint-Gaudens at ANS, 1981
    - E. Tomlinson Fort, 1991
    - John Ford Jr., 1988-1989
    - Anne Barbeau Gardiner, 1989-1990
    - Braden K. Frieder, 1992-1996
    - Jaroslav Folda, 1989-1995
    - Cory Gillilland, 1983-1997
    - Peter Gaspar, 1980-1990
    - Mario Gomes Marques, 1982-1990
    - Richard A. Goldthwaite, 1993-1996
    - Dieter Girgensohn, 1995
    - Cecile Morrisson, 1996
    - Jens Christian Moesgaard, 1993-1998
    - Scott Miller, 1987Henry Grunthal – First Grunthal lecture, 1999
    - Philip Grierson, 1981-2000
    - Kathryn Greenthal, 1984-1986
    - Judith Nolan, 1995
    - Joseph Veach Noble, 1997
    - Christopher E. Neuzil, 1989
    - John Munro, 1984-1990
    - Reinhold Mueller, 1981-1998
    - Gregory W. Ogletree, 1987
    - Edward J. Olszewski, 1985-1989
    - Lauris Olson, 1986-1989
  - Box 4 of 13
    - Roberto Pesant, 1980-1993
    - Patrick Perin, 1990-1993
    - M. Michel Pastoureau, 1981
    - Paley/Price Productions, 1994
    - Elizabeth J.E. Pirie, 1982
    - Debra Pincus, 1987-2000
    - Ira Rezak, 1984-1995
    - Bernard F. Reilly, 1986
    - Ebenezer Quarcoopome, 1985-1986
    - John Porteous, 1985-1992
    - Arent Pol, 1999
    - Arent Pol, 1990-1995
    - Mercedes Rueda Sabater, 1992-1996
    - Kathryn L. Reyerson, 1980
    - Charles Rosenberg, 1999
    - Dennis Romano, 1997
    - Louise B. Robbert, 1983-1996
    - Marjan Scharloo, 1990-1994
    - Sharon Salvadori – Summer Seminar, 1992
    - Andrea Saccocci, 1982-1996
    - Peter Spufford, 1979-1998
    - Susan Spinale, 1998
    - Arnold Spaer, 1980-1981
    - David Sorenson, 1990
    - Marika Somogyi, 1991
    - Carlos Baptista da Silva, 1997
    - Deborah J. Shepherd, 1981-1994
    - Andrew Stednitz, 1987-1988
    - Gilbert Stack, 1991-1999
    - Paolo Squatriti, 1988-1992
    - Christian Stoess – Mainz coins, 1986-1988
    - Rudolf C. Sterback, 1987
    - Wolfgang Steguweit, 1994-1996
    - Landon Thomas, 1994
    - James O. Sweeny, 1985
    - Stanislaw Suchodolski, 1984-1993
    - Thayer Tolles, 1995-1996
    - James Todesca, 1987-1999
    - Kevin Uhalde, 1997
    - Elizabeth Turnauer, 1997
    - Mark Tulloss, 1992
    - Lucia Travaini, 1985-1989
    - Paolo Visona, 1989-1992
    - Louis Waldman, 1990-1999
    - Mel Wacks, 1983-1995
    - Lisa Wolverton, 1995-1998
    - Martin Wolfe, 1981-1996
    - Gareth Williams, 1999
    - Diane Wolf – Commission of Fine Arts, 1987
    - Nancy Wicker, 1994
    - Gregory Whittington, 1987
    - H. Bartlett Wells, 1981-1988
    - Peter S. Wells, 1986-1989
    - Andrew Watson, 1998
    - Robert A. Weinman, 1988-1990
    - Michael Crevan – The Medal Maker film, 1996-1997
    - Inquiries – Medieval, 1996
    - Inquiries – Medals, 1991
    - Inquiries – Medals, 1997
    - Inquiries – Medieval & general, 1997
    - Inquiries – Medieval & general, 1998
    - Inquiries – Medals, 1998
    - Inquiries – Medals, 1998
    - NYNC (New York Numismatic Club), 1996
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1996
    - NYNC (New York Numismatic Club), 1997
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1997
    - NYNC (New York Numismatic Club), 1998
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association), 1998
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1998 (1 of 2)
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1998 (2 of 2)
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) - Registration, 1998
    - Kay stycas, 1996-1997
    - Summer Seminar, 1993
    - Summer Seminar, 1994
    - Summer Seminar, 1995
    - Summer Seminar, 1996
    - Summer Seminar, 1997
    - John T. Paoletti, 1994
    - Garland Publishing – Medieval England encyclopedia, 1989-1997
    - Excavation coins, 1988
    - Gritille excavation, 1992-1985
    - Cyprus casts, 1990
    - Verona hoard, 1991
    - Medieval Academy exhibit – Trade coins, 1997
  - Box 5 of 13
    - Hofstra University exhibit – Pope Innocent III, 1997
    - Anglo Saxon coinage, 1985
    - National Technical University of Athens – Symposium, 1988
    - Library Journal reviews, 1988
    - American Early Medieval Studies, 1991
    - ANS conferences, 1989
    - Silk Route (with two photographs of Stahl at site)
    - TEAMS Medieval coins slide set, 1988-1991
    - Colonel Bliss medal of 1849 (includes photographs), 1984
    - U.S. Mint –Citizens Commemorative Coin Advisory Committee, 1993
    - Mantua, 1995-1996
    - Alice-Mary Talbot – Pre-publication review, 1998
    - Survey of Numismatic Research, 1997
    - David R. Lit – gift of Abraham Lincoln plaster by Brenner, 1986-1988
    - Queer Middle Ages conference, 1998
    - COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference) and AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association) - Adenda, 1997 (includes photographs of Stahl and others)
    - COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference) – AMSA/BAMS show, 1997
    - Mantua, 1995-1996
    - Victor David Brenner at ANS, 1986-1988
    - Notre Dame – John Van Egan, 1995-1996
    - News on the Rialto, 1985-1996
    - NYINC (New York International Numismatic Convention), 1996-1999
    - New York Public Library
    - Medieval Club of New York, 1986-1994
    - Medieval and Early Modern Data Bank – Martha Howell, 1985
    - Museums Council of New York City, 1982-1985
    - Museum of Early Southern Decorative Arts – C.C. Wright, 1996
    - Monticello, 1996, 1999
    - Le Club Francais de la Medaille, 1981
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1983-1996
    - International Congress on Medieval Studies – Kalamazoo, 1992
    - National Academy of Design, 1983-1984
    - Report on Medieval Studies at Minnesota – John Leyerle, 1988
    - MWNA (Medieval World Numismatic Association), 1988
    - OMSA (Orders and Medals Society of America), 1988
    - New-York Historical Society, 1994
    - New York Council for the Humanities, 1994-1995
    - National Gallery of Art, 1983-1985
    - Society for the Study of the Crusades and the Latin East, 1983-1996
    - Society of Medalists, 1986-1987
    - Society for French History Studies (empty folder)
    - University of Peru, 1984-1990
    - Renaissance Society of America, 1985
    - University of Pennsylvania – Stahl biographical information for newsletter, 1986
    - Pen & Brush, Inc., 1996
    - Old World Archaeology Newsletter, 1981-1989
    - Medals – Mostly newsletters of the Modern Art Foundry, 1978-1984
    - Medal producers – including catalogs and promotional materials, 1980s
    - Lynn White Society, 1993
    - U.S. Mint – Silver commemorative dollar, 1990
    - Udine – Convegno on the Art Medal, 1997
    - SSHMA (Society for the Study of Homosexuality in the Middle Ages, 1991-1999
    - Artist portfolios, 1991
    - Yale – Loan of Tripolis hoard, 1996
    - Wolfsonian Research Center, 1989-1998
    - Meetings, papers, etc., 1980-1993
    - ANA (American Numismatic Association), 1983-1998
  - Box 6 of 13
    - AVISTA (Association Villard de Honnecourt for the Interdisciplinary Study of Medieval Technology, Science, and Art), 1995-1999
    - American Philosophical Society, 1995
    - AHA (American Historical Association), 1997-1998
    - Barnard College, 1987-1990
    - ANA (American Numismatic Association) – Centennial Medal, 1989-1991
    - AMES (Associazione Medaglistica Esaltazioni)
    - American Museum of Natural History, 1981
    - Bennington College – Field Work Term, 1989-1998
    - CAM (Collectors of Art Medals), 1972
    - Byzantine studies, 1984, 1987
    - Brookgreen Gardens, 1985-1997
    - British Art Medal Society, 1993-1999
    - Center for Medieval and Early Renaissance Studies – Binghamton, 1990
    - Colonial Williamsburg, 1995
    - Coin clubs, 1995
    - Cloisters, 1995
    - Coin of the Year – World Coin News, 1998-1999
    - CARA (Centers and Regional Associations), 1981-1988
    - Columbia seminar, 1984-1986
    - Confederate MBR newsletter, 1996
    - Computerized Inventory of American Sculpture, 1983-1988
    - Economic History Association, 1982-1984
    - CUNY (Includes Spinola medal project review), 1985, 1990
    - CRAM (Centre de Recherches Archeologiques Medievales, 1990
    - Fine Arts Federation of New York, 1991
    - Deutsche Medaillengesellschaft
    - Gladys Krieble Delmas, 1996
    - Dumbarton Oaks, 1981-1985
    - Fraunces Tavern, 1983-1988
    - Fordham, 1981-1996
    - Frick Collection, 1997
    - Paul Hennefeld, et. al. – The Native – Gay history and people on coins, 1982
    - Haskins Society, 1987-1993
    - HAS (Hispanic Society of America), 1987
    - Hudson River Museum, 1985
    - IFA-NYU (Institute of Fine Arts – New York University), 1995
    - ICMA (International Center of Medieval Art, Inc.), 1987-1996
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1999
    - Italian Art Society News, 1988-1994
    - Lithuanian Numismatic Association, 1984
    - Beaux Arts Medal in America funding, 1987
    - Sam (?) – Pratt Medals, Medallions, and Coins – Slide show text
    - Richman (?) – Draft of Daniel Chester French paper or talk
    - AMSA (American Medallic Sculpture Association – Exhibits, 1987
    - Yvonne Korshak – 1988
    - Javier Gimeno – 1987
    - George J. Fuld and Barry Tayman, 1987
    - Alan Stahl – COAC – Commentary, 1987
    - Speakers – Medal in America, 1987
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – General - (has photographs including Stahl), 1987
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Entries, 1987
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Public relations, 1987
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Paris delegates, 1987
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Finances, 1987
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Program, 1987
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) - Medal – Mico Kaufman, 1986
  - Box 7 of 13
    - Statue of Liberty Medal, 1986
    - Statue of Liberty Medal – Public relations, 1985-1987
    - Statue of Liberty Medal competition, 1985
    - Statue of Liberty Exhibit – Canceled, 1986
    - 125th Anniversary Medal – Competition, 1982
    - 125th Anniversary Medal – Competition – Jovine, 1982
    - 125th Anniversary Medal – Competition – Public relations, 1982
    - Food and Agriculture Organization – World Food Day medal, 1984
    - Thomas R. Martin, 1990
    - Bradley McLain, 1995
    - Jerome E. Singerman, 1999
    - Martha A. McCrory, 1996
    - Eleonora Luciano, 1995-1998
    - M. Claude Lorrren, 1990
    - Harold V. Livermore, 1988
    - N.J. Mayhew, 1988-1995
    - Jeffrey P. Mass, 1986-1998
    - D.M. Metcalf – Ashmolean Museum, 1980-1998
    - Novella Vismara, 1993
    - David T. Owsley, 1982-1993
    - ANS Members, etc., 1993-1999
    - Sculptors, 1984-1998
    - Collections – Medieval, 1982-1999
    - Collections – Decorations – Scholars, 1984-1996
    - Producers of medals – Including Medallic Arts, 1991
    - Collectors – Medals, 1982-1990
    - Scholars – Medieval, 1980-1999
    - Dealers, 1983-1995
    - John Adams, 1999
    - Philip Attwood, 1988-1996
    - Ermanno A. Arslan, 1982-1996
    - Benjamin Arbel, 1989-1994
    - Elizabeth Ayer, 1988
    - John L. Barton, 1978
    - Julian Baker, 1998-1999
    - Barbara A. Baxter, 1987-1999
    - Allen G. Berman, 1982
    - Peter Berghaus, 1985-1994
    - Simon Bendall, 1981-1983
    - Paul Z. Bedoukian, 1987-1988
    - Mark Blackburn, 1992-1994
    - Constance Hoffman Berman, 1981-1990
    - Barbara S. Bowers, 1990-1995
    - M. Marc Bompaire, 1993
    - Thomas W. Blomquist, 1980-1990
    - Giles F. Carter, 1986-1995
    - Maria Ana da Camara, 1989-1991
    - Bruno Callegher, 1997-1998
    - Patricia F. Brown, 1995
    - Elizabeth A.R. Brown, 1980-1982
  - Box 8 of 13
    - David G. Briggs, 1983
    - Jeremiah Brady, 1982
    - Gene Bowles, 1982-1985
    - Barbara Cook, 1990, 1994
    - Remie Constable, 1991-1995
    - Jonathan Conant, 1999
    - Robert D. Coleman, 1996
    - Elvira E. Clain-Stefanelli, 1995
    - Salvatore Ciriacono, 1990-1997
    - Madame Jacques Charpentier, 1994
    - Marianne Letterie, 1993-1995
    - Sarah E. Lawrence – The Jewish Museum, 1994-1998
    - Frederic C. Lane, 1981-1983
    - Coin inquiries, 1990
    - Medal inquiries, 1990
    - Loose pages from an article (?) on medals – Durer, Buonarotti, etc.
    - Coin inquiries, 1995
    - Louis Zara - Pisanello medal – Photographs, 1974
    - R. Julian photo order – and lists related to U.S. Mint, 1974
    - Barbara A. Baxter – Bogardus, 1989
    - Gorringe-Vanderbilt Obelisk medal, 1983
    - Victor David Brenner exhibit, 1995
    - Medieval Monastery – University of Minnesota, 1985-1988
    - Sweden – Lagerquist
    - Grosso (?)
    - University of Regina, 1984-1985
    - Mark Edward Sekelsky hoard, 1980
    - P.&P. Santamaria florins, 1979
    - Milan computer meeting, 1984
    - Beaux Arts Medal in America exhibit, 1987-1993
    - Columbus conference (1992), 1987-1991
    - Henry Maguire – Speculum, 1993-1995
    - COAC – Indian Peace Medals, 1991
    - The Insular Tradition – Karkov, et. al. - Review, 1995
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Indian Peace Medals, 1990-1991
    - American Numismatic Association – Indian Peace Medals exhibit, 1991
    - Medieval Europe, 1992
    - Renaissance Medal Exhibit, 1992-1994
    - U.S. Congress – Commemorative coinage testimony, 1995
    - Piranesi prints, 1994
    - Coin inquiries, 1994
    - Medal inquiries, 1994
    - Sutton Hoo, 1989-1990
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Forms for action on returning medals, 1994 (1 of 2)
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) – Forms for action on returning medals, 1994 (2 of 2)
  - Box 9 of 13
    - Numismatique Merovingienne, Fonds Bourgey, Alan Stahl
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society), 1992
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society), 1993
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society) – Medal competition, 1992
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society) – Exhibition committee, 1992
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society) – Sculpture review, 1992
    - NSS (National Sculpture Society) – Medal competition, 1994
    - Curatorial memos, 1972-1999
    - Photography, 1999
    - General memos, 1979-1999
    - Accessions, 1989-1990
    - Education, 1995-1996
    - Exhibits, 1991?
    - Security, 1980-1990
    - AREV – Computerized coin database, 1995-1998
    - Auction sale catalog scanning project, 1998-1999
    - Development, 1986-1999
    - Photofile, 1992
    - Harry Fowler and other medal production, 1990-1996
    - Harry Bass coins, 1989
    - Dollar coin, 1998
    - Editorial, 1982-1997
    - Thefts
    - Purchases of medals, 1985-1992